Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
- Phonograph records
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 125-126), undated; bell_brothers_534; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 127-128), undated; bell_brothers_535; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 133-134), undated; bell_brothers_536; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 151-152), undated; bell_brothers_538; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 161-162), undated; bell_brothers_539; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 185-186), undated; bell_brothers_540; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 187-188), undated; bell_brothers_541; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 197-198), undated; bell_brothers_570; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 199-200), undated; bell_brothers_542; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 201-202), undated; bell_brothers_571; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 203-204), undated; bell_brothers_543; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 209-210), undated; bell_brothers_572; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 213-214), undated; bell_brothers_573; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 215-216), undated; bell_brothers_544; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 231-232), undated; bell_brothers_574; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 237-238), undated; bell_brothers_546; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 255), undated; bell_brothers_547; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 261-262), undated; bell_brothers_548; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists(No. 135-136), undated; bell_brothers_537; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists(No. 221-222), undated; bell_brothers_545; vinyl disc
  - Forward March, featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 249-250), undated; bell_brothers_616; vinyl disc
  - Forward March, featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 253-254), undated; bell_brothers_617; vinyl disc
  - Forward March, featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 263-264(, undated; bell_brothers_618; vinyl disc
  - Frank Morgan (No. 7), 10/12/1944; bell_brothers_503; vinyl disc
  - Frank Morgan (No. 9), 10/26/1944; bell_brothers_455; vinyl disc
  - Fred Waring (No. 415), 05/03/1945; bell_brothers_523; vinyl disc
  - Fred Waring Christmas Album (No. 60); Dinah Shore Christmas Card (No. 62), 1944; bell_brothers_576; vinyl disc
  - Frieda Hempel Interviewed, Stephri Fawsset, 05/23/1948; bell_brothers_117; lacquer on paper disc
  - "Frijsh: Valse, (Danish) ", undated; bell_brothers_267; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 2), undated; bell_brothers_032; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 3), undated; bell_brothers_014; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 4), undated; bell_brothers_028; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 5), undated; bell_brothers_010; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 6), undated; bell_brothers_005; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 8), undated; bell_brothers_006; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 9), undated; bell_brothers_012; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 10), undated; bell_brothers_015; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 12), undated; bell_brothers_016; shellac disc
  - Front Page Headlines; Speed And Double Speed (No. 13), undated; bell_brothers_026; shellac disc
  - G. I. Jive: Jill (No. 1767-768), undated; bell_brothers_486; vinyl disc
  - G. I. Journal, Bob Hope, Bette Davis, Arthur Treacher, Tony Seven; Bob Hope, Bette Davis, Arthur Treacher, Tony Seven (Series H-19, No. 89), undated; bell_brothers_614; vinyl disc
  - Gaetano Maria Schiassi: Christmas Symphony, Fiedler (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_251; shellac disc
  - Gaetano Maria Schiassi: Christmas Symphony, Fiedler (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_252; shellac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_324; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_325; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_326; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_327; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 5), undated; bell_brothers_328; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 6), undated; bell_brothers_329; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 7), undated; bell_brothers_330; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 8), undated; bell_brothers_331; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 9), undated; bell_brothers_332; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 10), undated; bell_brothers_333; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 11), undated; bell_brothers_334; vitrolac disc
  - Gay: The Beggar's Opera (Part 12), undated; bell_brothers_335; vitrolac disc
  - Gildersleeve (No. 61), 10/22/1944; bell_brothers_464; vinyl disc
  - Gliere: String Quartet in A Major (Parts 1 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_172; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Gliere: String Quartet in A Major (Parts 2 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_173; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Gliere: String Quartet in A Major (Part 5); Abel: Sonata - Flute, Violas and Harpsichord (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_174; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Gliere: String Quartet in A Major, (Part 6); Abel: Sonata - Flute, Violas and Harpsichord (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_175; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Glinka: Sonata in D Minor (Parts 2 and 4), 08/10/1941; bell_brothers_207; lacquer on glass disc
  - Glinka: The Lark, undated; bell_brothers_300; on shellac disc
  - Gluck: Armide, [Selections], (Parts 5 and 7), 04/07/1943; bell_brothers_197; lacquer on glass disc
  - Gluck: Don Juan Ballet, Victor Chamber Orchestra, (Disc 1), undated; bell_brothers_340; vitrolac disc
  - Gluck: Don Juan Ballet, Victor Chamber Orchestra, (Disc 2), undated; bell_brothers_341; vitrolac disc
  - Gluck-Mottl: Ballet Suite, Boston Symphony Orchestra, (Part 1), 03/24/1940; bell_brothers_336; vitrolac disc
  - Gluck-Mottl: Ballet Suite, Boston Symphony Orchestra, (Part 2), 03/24/1940; bell_brothers_337; vitrolac disc
  - Gluck-Mottl: Ballet Suite, Boston Symphony Orchestra, (Part 3), 03/24/1940; bell_brothers_338; vitrolac disc
  - Gluck-Mottl: Ballet Suite, Boston Symphony Orchestra, (Part 4), 03/24/1940; bell_brothers_339; vitrolac disc
  - Gossec: Symphony In D, 2; Mozart: Symphony No. 22 C Major, undated; bell_brothers_043; lacquer on glass disc
  - Greek Minnie, undated; bell_brothers_116; lacquer on glass disc
  - Green Grass Grows All Around, undated; bell_brothers_062; lacquer on glass disc
  - Grieg: Der Skreg en Fugl, I Heard the Gull [sic], With a Waterlilly, Frijsh, undated; bell_brothers_319; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, Flagstad (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_311; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, Flagstad (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_312; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, Flagstad (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_313; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, The Tryst, Flagstad (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_314; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, Love, Flagstad (Part 5), undated; bell_brothers_315; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, Love, Flagstad (Part 6), undated; bell_brothers_316; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, Flagstad (Part 7), undated; bell_brothers_317; vitrolac disc
  - Grieg: Haugtussa, Op. 67, Flagstad (Part 8), undated; bell_brothers_318; vitrolac disc
  - Guy Lombardo (No. 45), 12/16/1944; bell_brothers_481; vinyl disc
  - Guy Lombardo Program: MS Hope Chest Special with celebrity appeals (WOR Record No. 2), 1958; bell_brothers_796; vinyl disc
  - Gypsy Princess (Parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_052; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hahn: Piano Quintet in F sharp Minor (Parts 1 and 3), 06/07/1935; bell_brothers_167; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hahn: Piano Quintet in F sharp Minor (Parts 2 and 4), 06/07/1935; bell_brothers_168; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hahn: Piano Quintet in F sharp Minor (Parts 5 and 7), 06/07/1935; bell_brothers_169; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hahn: Piano Quintet in F sharp Minor (Parts 6 and 8), 06/07/1935; bell_brothers_170; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hallawleart [sic], O. G. Q., undated; bell_brothers_102; lacquer on glass disc
  - Harry James and His Orchestra; Ken Griffin at the Hammond Organ; Orton and Rarig, Duo Piano Team (WPS Record 211), undated; bell_brothers_788; vinyl disc
  - Haydn: String Quartet, Op. 64, No. 5, Lark, Movement 1, Hungarian Quartet, 05/15/1950; bell_brothers_273; vinyl disc
  - Haydn: String Quartet, Op. 64, No. 5, Lark, Movement 2 (Part 1) Hungarian Quartet, 05/15/1950; bell_brothers_274; vinyl disc
  - Haydn: String Quartet, Op. 64, No. 5, Lark, Movement 2 (Part 2), Movement 3, Hungarian Quartet, 05/16/1950; bell_brothers_275; vinyl disc
  - Haydn: String Quartet, Op. 64, No. 5, Lark, Movement 4, Hungarian Quartet, 05/15/1950; bell_brothers_276; vinyl disc
  - Heidi, NBC - Television Musical (Parts 1 and 2), 10/01/1955; bell_brothers_435; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Here's to Romance, (Lemon) (No. 12), 08/17/1944; bell_brothers_456; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Claude Gordon (Full identification); Lex Baxter (Outpatient care) (25 No. 317-318), 11/22/1952; 11/29/1952; bell_brothers_597; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Dave Rose (Korean Insurance) (25 No. 325), 01/17/1953; bell_brothers_598; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Eddy Howard (Hire the handicapped); Mindy Carson (Proper care of your VA checks) (37 No. 475-476), undated; bell_brothers_603; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Felicia Sanders Disability pay); Three Sons (GI training pay) (38 No. 484-485), undated; bell_brothers_604; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Frankie Carle (Tips for new veterans); Jeff Chandler (Your GI insurance) (35 No. 449-450), undated; bell_brothers_602; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Jimmy Wakely (How to get a GI loan); Buddy Morrow (Training for disable veterans) (28 No. 352-353), 07/25/1953; 08/01/1953; bell_brothers_600; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Johnny Green (C number) George Cates (GI insurance) (24 No 312-312A), 10/07/1952; 10/18/1952; bell_brothers_596; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Lou Busch Buying that GI home); VA spot announcements, Jerry Vale; Andre Previn; Lawrence Welk; Harry Zimmerman; Morris Stoloff; Lou Busch, Johnny Ray; Billy May; Coleman Hawkins; Milton Berle; Diahanne Carroll; Bob Hope; Mitch Miller; Louis Prima (42 No. 534), undated; bell_brothers_605; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Paul Weston (GI on job training); Tennessee Ernie (Korean GI training pay) (27 No. 343-344), 05/23/1953; 05/30/1953; bell_brothers_599; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Tex Williams (Korean GI insurance); Francis Scott (GI loans) (28 No. 356-366), 08/22/1953; 08/29/1953; bell_brothers_601; vinyl disc
  - Here's to Veterans: Vaughn Monroe (Change of address); Buddy Morrow (New GI insurance) (24 No. 306-307), 08/26/1952; 09/02/1952; bell_brothers_595; vinyl disc
  - Herman Gertz [sic]: Symphony in F (Parts 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_201; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Herman Gertz [sic]: Symphony in F (Parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_198; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hit Parade (No 78), 04/22/1944; bell_brothers_478; vinyl disc
  - Hit Parade (No. 134), 05/12/1945; bell_brothers_521; vinyl disc
  - Holbrook: Suite for Strings (Parts 1 and 3), 10/05/1941; bell_brothers_171; lacquer on glass disc
  - Hollywood’s open house (No. 7 and 11), 12/07/1944; 01/18/1945; bell_brothers_451; vinyl disc
  - Hollywood’s open house (No. 18), undated; bell_brothers_452; vinyl disc
  - Holst - Fugal Concerto (Parts 1 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_048; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Holst - Fugal Concerto (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_049; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Homer Keller: Serenade for Clarinet and Strings, American Composers Orchestra, 04/30/1940; bell_brothers_390; vitrolac disc
  - Howard Hanson: American Dance for Bassoon and String Orchestra, Burrill Phillips, undated; bell_brothers_388; vitrolac disc
  - Howard Hanson: Music For The Theater (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_383; vitrolac disc
  - Howard Hanson: Music For The Theater (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_385; vitrolac disc
  - Howard Hanson: Music For The Theater (Part 2A), undated; bell_brothers_384; vitrolac disc
  - Howard Hanson: Music For The Theater (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_386; vitrolac disc
  - Howard Hanson: Music For The Theater (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_387; vitrolac disc
  - Howard Hanson: Rhapsody for Oboe and Strings, Wayne Barlow, undated; bell_brothers_391; vitrolac disc
  - Hugh [sic] Porter: Ukrainian Suite (Parts 1 and 3), 02/20/1940; bell_brothers_188; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hugh [sic] Porter: Ukrainian Suite (Part 2), 02/20/1940; bell_brothers_189; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Hugo Wolf: Gebet, Lotte Lehmann, undated; bell_brothers_220; shellac disc
  - Hugo Wolf: Nun Lass uns Frieden Schliesse, Lotte Lehmann, undated; bell_brothers_221; shellac disc
  - Hummel: Quartet No. 1 (Part 2), 08/16/1941; bell_brothers_178; lacquer on glass disc
  - Hymns From Home, Will Moore (No. 183-184), undated; bell_brothers_484; vinyl disc
  - I Can’t Give You Anything but Love Baby; Stomping at the Savoy, undated; bell_brothers_105; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - I Sustain the [sic. TO] Wings Broadcasts (No. 1 and 2), 08/14/1943; 08/21/1943; 08/28/1943; 09/04/1943; 09/11/1943; bell_brothers_002; acetate on aluminum disc
  - I Sustain the [sic. TO] Wings Broadcasts (No. 3 and 4), 09/11/1943; 10/02/1943; 10/09/1943; bell_brothers_001; acetate aluminum disc
  - Information Please (No. 20), undated; bell_brothers_480; vinyl disc
  - Intermezzo (No. 9), undated; bell_brothers_454; vinyl disc
  - J. S. Bach: Fugue in G Major - The Jig Fugue, E. Power Biggs, undated; bell_brothers_382; vitrolac disc
  - J. S. Bach: Fugue in G Minor - The Little, E. Power Biggs, undated; bell_brothers_381; vitrolac disc
  - J. S. Bach: Passacaglia and Fugue in C Minor, E. Power Biggs (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_376; vitrolac disc
  - J. S. Bach: Passacaglia and Fugue in C Minor, E. Power Biggs (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_377; vitrolac disc
  - J. S. Bach: Passacaglia and Fugue in C Minor, E. Power Biggs (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_378; vitrolac disc
  - J. S. Bach: Sonata in G Major, 1st and 2nd Movement, Spalding, undated; bell_brothers_374; vitrolac disc
  - J. S. Bach: Sonata in G Major, 3rd and 4th Movement, Spalding, undated; bell_brothers_375; vitrolac disc
  - Jack Benny (No. 18), 04/09/1944; bell_brothers_459; vinyl disc
  - Jack Benny (No. 41), undated; bell_brothers_507; vinyl disc
  - Jack Benny (No. 74), 11/19/1944; bell_brothers_467; vinyl disc
  - Jascha Heifetz playing Mairzy Doats with Donald Voorhees and the Bell Telephone Orchestra, 03/06/1944; bell_brothers_268; vinyl disc
  - Jeanette MacDonald and Nelson Eddy, 11/25/1946; bell_brothers_045; lacquer aluminum disc
  - Jill's All Time Juke Box (Series H-46, No. 29, undated; bell_brothers_530; vinyl disc
  - Jimmy Dorsey and his Orchestra; The Andrews sisters (With Vic Schoen and his Orchestra) (WPS), 03/16/1947; bell_brothers_792; vinyl disc
  - Join the Navy (No. 45-46), undated; bell_brothers_494; vinyl disc
  - Join the Navy (No. 88), undated; bell_brothers_581; vinyl disc
  - Join the Navy (No. 95-96), undated; bell_brothers_495; vinyl disc
  - Join the Navy (No. 119-120), undated; bell_brothers_582; vinyl disc
  - Jones and Herman Replacing Waltz Time (No. 55), 09/27/1944; bell_brothers_462; vinyl disc
  - Joseph Brunnel [sic]: Chaconne, by Couperin; Fantasie Une Jeune Fillette, Du Caurroy, undated; bell_brothers_310; shellac disc
  - Joseph Brunnel [sic]: Le Moulin De Rio, Perotin, undated; bell_brothers_309; shellac disc
  - Joseph Davis: Tribute to Russia (Part 7), 06/27/1943; bell_brothers_044; lacquer on glass disc
  - Jubilee (Series H-1, No. 127), undated; bell_brothers_528; vinyl disc
  - Jubilee (Series H-11, No. 123), undated; bell_brothers_527; vinyl disc
  - Juon: Viola Sonata (Parts 2 and 5), undated; bell_brothers_163; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Juon: Viola Sonata, (Parts 3 and 6), undated; bell_brothers_164; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Kate Smith #67 (Part 2), 06/02/1944; 06/16/1944; bell_brothers_577; on vinyl disc
  - Kollege [sic] of Musical Knowledge (No. 104), 10/18/1944; bell_brothers_475; vinyl disc
  - Kollege [sic] of Musical Knowledge (No. 95), 08/16/1944; bell_brothers_472; vinyl disc
  - La Vie En Rose; Lia For and Without, undated; bell_brothers_083; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Lionel Hampton: Flying Home (Part 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_042; lacquer on glass disc
  - Locatelli: Theme and Variations (Part 2); Mozart: Overture Ascanis [sic] in Alba, 08/07/1941; bell_brothers_165; lacquer on glass disc
  - Lone Ranger (No. 936) (Part 2), 01/25/1939; bell_brothers_759; vitrolac disc
  - Mail call (Series H-1, No. 105), undated; bell_brothers_483; vinyl disc
  - Mail Call (No. 109), undated; bell_brothers_520; vinyl disc
  - Mail Call - Linda Darnell (No. 114), undated; bell_brothers_476; vinyl disc
  - Major Bowes (No. 18), 04/06/1944; bell_brothers_458; vinyl disc
  - Major Bowes (No. 58), undated; bell_brothers_607; vinyl disc
  - Mamus Friends (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_063; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Mamus Friends (Parts 2 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_064; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 5 and 6), undated; bell_brothers_501; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 35 and 36), undated; bell_brothers_502; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 43 and 44), undated; bell_brothers_583; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 45 and 46), undated; bell_brothers_584; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 69 and 70), undated; bell_brothers_585; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 71 and 72), undated; bell_brothers_586; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 77 and 78), undated; bell_brothers_587; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 81 and 82), undated; bell_brothers_588; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 83 and 84), undated; bell_brothers_589; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 85 and 86), undated; bell_brothers_590; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 95 and 96), undated; bell_brothers_591; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 119 and 120), undated; bell_brothers_592; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 129 and 130), undated; bell_brothers_593; vinyl disc
  - Manhattan Melodies (No. 131 and 132), undated; bell_brothers_594; vinyl disc
  - Manon, 01/13/1940; bell_brothers_736; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - March of Dimes Campaign (1944): Music Fight for Infantile Paralysis, Frank Sinatra with Axel Stordahl and His Orchestra, 12/26/1944; bell_brothers_448; vinyl disc
  - March of Dimes Campaign (1945): National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis presents Clark Gable - Basil O’Connor, Introduced by John W. Vandercook; Music Fights for Infantile Paralysis, Raymond Scott and His Orchestra, 01/14/1945; 01/31/1945; bell_brothers_797; vinyl disc
  - March of Dimes (1946): Stars on Parade, 01/03/1956; 01/31/1956; bell_brothers_798; vinyl disc
  - Marian Anderson: But the Lord is Merciful of His Own, (St. Paul), undated; bell_brothers_293; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: Crucifixion, undated; bell_brothers_297; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: Gestillte Sehnsucht, Brahms, Symphony premiere (Part 1, disc 1), undated; bell_brothers_364; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: Gestillte Sehnsucht, Brahms, Symphony premiere (Part 1, disc 2), undated; bell_brothers_366; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: Gestillte Sehnsucht, Brahms, Symphony premiere (Part 2, disc 1), undated; bell_brothers_365; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: Gestillte Sehnsucht, Brahms, Symphony premiere (Part 2, disc 2), undated; bell_brothers_367; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: He Shall Feed His Flock, from Messiah, by Handel, undated; bell_brothers_294; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: O, Rest in the Lord, from Elijah, by Mendelssohn, undated; bell_brothers_295; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: Oh, Rock Me Slow and Easy; I Am Seeking For a City, undated; bell_brothers_292; shellac disc
  - Marian Anderson: The Messiah, He Shall be Despised, by Handel, undated; bell_brothers_296; shellac disc
  - Martino, undated; bell_brothers_200; on shellac disc
  - Measure for Measure, WNYC The Shakespeare Festival, Shakespeare Theater (Parts 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_436; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Measure for Measure, WNYC The Shakespeare Festival, Shakespeare Theater (Parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_437; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Mendelssohn: Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, J. M. Sanroma and Boston Pops Orchestra (1st Movement, Part 1), 11/16/1939; bell_brothers_430; vinyl disc
  - Mendelssohn: Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, J. M. Sanroma and Boston Pops Orchestra (1st Movement Part 2, 2nd Movement, Part 1), 11/16/1939; bell_brothers_431; vinyl disc
  - Mendelssohn: Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, J. M. Sanroma and Boston Pops Orchestra (2nd Movement, Part 2), 11/16/1939; bell_brothers_432; vinyl disc
  - Mendelssohn: Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, J. M. Sanroma and Boston Pops Orchestra, (3rd Movement, Part 1), 11/16/1939; bell_brothers_433; shellac disc
  - Mendelssohn: Concerto, Boston Pops Orchestra, (Disc 5), 11/16/1939; bell_brothers_434; shellac disc